<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Europe on AAN World News</title><link>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/tags/europe/</link><description>Recent content in Europe on AAN World News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 21:27:37 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/tags/europe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hot pursuit through Chernarus, thieves apprehended</title><link>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2022/03/chase-in-zelenogorsk-thieves-apprehended/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 21:27:37 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2022/03/chase-in-zelenogorsk-thieves-apprehended/</guid><description>Pursuit ended north of Zelenogorsk with pickup smashing into a tree on the side of the road. (AAN World News)
Reckless pursuit through central Chernarus I was going back home when a reckless pickup swung by me in Chernogorsk, immediately followed by 2 Militia cars with sirens on. Without any thought, I turned around and joined the chase, hoping to get some good photos.
The suspect was heading north through Nadiezdino and Rogowo towards Kabanino.</description></item><item><title>Russian Forces leave Chernarus</title><link>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2022/01/russian-forces-leave-chernarus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2022/01/russian-forces-leave-chernarus/</guid><description>Last Russian Forces crossed the Russia-Chernarus border, leaving to Russia. (AAN News)
Today, Russian Forces left Chernarus entirely.
This is the result of talks between Chedaks and Russians, held in December. On 27th December, Russians agreed their Armed Forces to leave Chernarus. However, some civilian personnel, including government advisors, will remain there for an undisclosed period of time.
Chedaks grateful for help Chedaki leader, Serafim Smirnov, expressed his gratitude towards Russian brothers.</description></item><item><title>Military train carrying vehicles arrived in Zelenogorsk</title><link>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2022/03/long-military-train-in-zelenogorsk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 07:16:37 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2022/03/long-military-train-in-zelenogorsk/</guid><description>Military train with vehicles arrived in Zelenogorsk. (courtesy of an anonymous person)
Military train came from Russia Over a dozen cargo wagons and several for carrying vehicle arrived in Zelenogorsk today morning. The train drove through Chernarus at night to avoid disruption in local transport.
Russia claims the transport contains uniforms, helmets, vests, AKs and other personal weapons, ammunition, fragmentation, smoke and stun grenades as well as a bunch of explosives, as there is a shortage of these in Chedaki forces.</description></item><item><title>Anti-Chedaki protests in Chernogorsk</title><link>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2021/06/anti-chedaki-protests-in-chernogorsk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 19:17:25 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2021/06/anti-chedaki-protests-in-chernogorsk/</guid><description>Militia deployed highly violent crowd control unit to deal with the riot. (courtesy of an anonymous citizen)
Dissatisfaction of Chernarus citizens grows Since Chedaks took power in Chernarus, discontent among the population grew instead of dying down. One could wonder why are they still unhappy if the government changed. And they are even more unhappy than ever before.
Today, over 500 people joined protest in Chernogorsk while government sources said there was a small protest of 30 citizens.</description></item><item><title>Czechia beats Russia in ice hockey</title><link>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/europe/2021/05/czechia-russia-ice-hockey-5-4/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 22:34:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/europe/2021/05/czechia-russia-ice-hockey-5-4/</guid><description>Optimism, disappointment, lack of faith in making up for losses and incredible joy after an unbelievable win are just a few of the vast range of emotions that Czech players gave their fans tonight.
Optimistic start and utter defeat Before the match, Czechia fans were quite optimistic. The rival was definitely within reach for a hard earned win. Czechs gained an advantage very early in the first period and the crowd at Prague arena went crazy.</description></item><item><title>NATO Statement on coup in Chernarus</title><link>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/europe/2021/05/nato-statement-on-chernarus-coup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 20:21:32 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/europe/2021/05/nato-statement-on-chernarus-coup/</guid><description>Following today&amp;rsquo;s coup in Chernarus and Russian Forces entering the country, NATO General Secretary called a press conference at 8 PM.
Russian-made coup in Chernarus &amp;ldquo;We believe the Chedaks were sponsored, armed and trained by Russia&amp;rdquo; - says General Secretary Magnus Odenberd - &amp;ldquo;Recent Russian Forces relocation near the Chernarus border. Moreover, Russian Forces entered Chernarus just hours after Chedaks captured Chernogorsk.&amp;rdquo;
No NATO country will recognize Chedakia &amp;ldquo;This is an unacceptable infringement of a European country sovereignty.</description></item><item><title>Russian Forces enter Chernarus</title><link>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2021/05/russian-forces-enter-chernarus/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 12:31:42 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2021/05/russian-forces-enter-chernarus/</guid><description>Russian forces on the move towards the Russia-Chernarus border. (BBN Global)
Following the successful Chedaki coup in Chernarus and proclamation of Chedaki Republic, Russian Defense Secretary Dimitry Strogonov recognized Chedakia and announced help package for the new government, including providing security during the transition.
Russian Forces enter Chernarus Today at 11 AM local time, Russian Forces crossed Chernarus border and moved to secure main cities and government buildings.</description></item><item><title>Chedaki coup in Chernarus successful</title><link>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2021/05/chedaki-coup-successful/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 11:02:13 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2021/05/chedaki-coup-successful/</guid><description>Chedaki flags flutter over the Chernarus. (AAN World News)
After weeks of skirmishes in Northern Chernarus, today Chedaki fighters surprised local Militia as well as Chernarus Defense Forces and stormed Chernogorsk, the capital city of Chernarus. They&amp;rsquo;ve quickly pushed Militia out of the city centre and surrounded the town hall. Quick negotiations took place between Chedaks and government authorities, while Militia tried to break through to the town hall. After 15 minutes it was over, the coup succeeded.</description></item><item><title>Brutal double murder in Berezino</title><link>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2021/04/berezino-brutal-murder/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 08:01:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2021/04/berezino-brutal-murder/</guid><description>Militia patrol arrived just to find dead bodies in a very disturbing scene. (photo courtesy of an anonymous citizen)
Disturbing morning violence This morning Berezino was shocked with brutal murder committed in a household in the central part of the town. Neighbors were woken up around 6 AM by gunshots.
&amp;ldquo;I heard the gunshots, I think there were at least 2 shooters, maybe more.&amp;rdquo; - says one of direct neighbors, who for obvious reason wanted to stay anonymous.</description></item><item><title>Shootout in Berezino, dozens killed</title><link>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2021/04/berezino-chedaks-militia-shootout/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 09:23:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2021/04/berezino-chedaks-militia-shootout/</guid><description>Militia secures the scene. Lada took heavy fire, but provided enough cover. Some blood and bodybags visible. (AAN World News)
Today at 7 AM, a heavy shootout occurred in the outskirts of Berezino Militia squad supported by a few local farmers were heading for the last known location of Chedaki fighters. They were ambushed in the forest 1 km west of Berezino. Shots were heard in the city as well as in surrounding villages.</description></item><item><title>Russia increases presence on Chernarus border</title><link>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/europe/2021/03/russia-increases-presence-on-chernarus-border/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 14:30:02 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/europe/2021/03/russia-increases-presence-on-chernarus-border/</guid><description>One of the redeployed brigades comes from Fapovo island, jets taking off and infantry loading into helicopters can be seen. (Russian MoD)
Russian MoD announced increase in the military presence on the Chernarus border as a response to rebels in northern Chernarus.
Rebels in Chernarus concern Russia &amp;ldquo;Chernarus cannot handle the rebels within their territory and we are concerned about our security.&amp;rdquo; says Colonel Anatolii Dragutin. &amp;ldquo;We have decided to move three motorized brigades near the border to prevent the rebels from illegally crossing into Russia.</description></item><item><title>Unknown rebels in rural areas</title><link>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2021/04/unknown-rebels-in-rural-areas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 17:31:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2021/04/unknown-rebels-in-rural-areas/</guid><description>Delivery truck full of goods was stolen from general goods store in Stary Sobor. (AAN World News)
Over the last days, there were multiple reports of paramilitary-like personnel in the woods in northern Chernarus. There are little details known right now, but our sources report shots were fired several times already, although no one was hurt in any way yet.
We&amp;rsquo;ve managed to reach one of the villagers who&amp;rsquo;d like to stay anonymous.</description></item><item><title>Workers strike in Chernogorsk's stink factory</title><link>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2021/03/strike-in-chernogorsk-factory/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 08:32:12 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://armaforces.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/chernarus/2021/03/strike-in-chernogorsk-factory/</guid><description>Strike at Chernogorsk&amp;rsquo;s stink factory is very civil and peaceful, Militia guards the order and supports the protesting workers. (AAN News)
Workers demand better pay and work conditions Tensions had been growing in Chernogorsk stink factory for the last couple of days. Workers were unhappy about their pay and work conditions, arguing that they should have additional healthcare days off. Moreover, their pay should be raised by at least 10% due to, in their opinion, exceptional performance and stink production rates last year.</description></item></channel></rss>