<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Specialist Correspondent on AAN World News</title><link>https://aan-news.proffer.dev/profiles/jacob-proffer/</link><description>Recent content in Specialist Correspondent on AAN World News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 08:44:17 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aan-news.proffer.dev/profiles/jacob-proffer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SECDEF Visits Greece</title><link>https://aan-news.proffer.dev/articles/secdef-visits-greece/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 08:44:17 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://aan-news.proffer.dev/articles/secdef-visits-greece/</guid><description>Security personnel surround SECDEF Mike Hammer as he arrives in Greece. (AAN World News)
Janus Security Contractors were on hand to provide escort security for the SECDEF as he makes his way across Greece. Reportedly his next stop will be in Iraq for a de-escalation briefing with the current PM of the nation. With the recent events that have taken place north east of Baghdad where a United Nations Air Outpost was destroyed by ISIS many are waiting for a favorable outcome for Iraq at the US&amp;rsquo;s expense.</description></item><item><title>Coalition Forces Respond to UN Plea</title><link>https://aan-news.proffer.dev/articles/coalition-forces-respond-to-un/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 18:11:26 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://aan-news.proffer.dev/articles/coalition-forces-respond-to-un/</guid><description>A U.S. Marine provides covering fire with a heavy machine gun. (AAN World News)
US and Coalition Combatant Commands have surged the current amount of troops on the ground in Iraq from 1,500 to almost 7,000 in response to the United Nations plea for help after on of its outposts responsible for aid in an area North East of Baghdad was attacked by ISIS. The question remains what the Coalition Forces will do with those numbers and where we will be a year from now.</description></item><item><title>NATO Forces Assist in Anizay</title><link>https://aan-news.proffer.dev/articles/us-military-assists-in-anizay/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 22:38:50 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://aan-news.proffer.dev/articles/us-military-assists-in-anizay/</guid><description>A NATO soldier provides overwatch in Landay. (AAN World News)
As the Islamic State poured into the northern regions of Anizay this past Friday, military forces and government backed militias were overwhelmed. With the capital and nearby cities under siege, civilians fled to the southern borders in an attempt to get out of the country.
A rapid response force, consisting of nearly 500 US soldiers and sailors, have arrived to defend the diplomatic embassy in Landay.</description></item><item><title>Flesh Eating Virus Hits California</title><link>https://aan-news.proffer.dev/articles/virus-hits-california/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 18:41:03 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://aan-news.proffer.dev/articles/virus-hits-california/</guid><description>Members of the CDC inside of the infectious zone. (AAN World News)
The Center for Disease Control confirmed on Friday that a family of three in California, found dead on Thursday afternoon, tested positive for a flesh eating virus.
Prior to the discovery, the Rudwells hadn&amp;rsquo;t been seen in days. The father, Aiden Rudwell, was a member of the Santa Catalina yacht club. After he missed multiple meetings without contact, the club president asked for a well-being check to be conducted.</description></item><item><title>Helicopter Crash Kills Four in Altis</title><link>https://aan-news.proffer.dev/articles/altis-helicopter-crash/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 17:47:59 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://aan-news.proffer.dev/articles/altis-helicopter-crash/</guid><description>Reporters next to the crashed KA-60 helicopter in northern Altis. (AAN World News)
AAN News reporter Mark Cole and cameraman Arthur Stark have tragically died in a helicopter crash alongside pilot Mark Hayes and co-pilot Jim Greers.
The helicopter took off from the NATO air force base shortly after 8am on Thursday and was on its way to a CSAT base on the east coast. Just over ten minutes later, it dropped from the radar screen and went down near a small village.</description></item><item><title>Blackwater in Cambodia</title><link>https://aan-news.proffer.dev/articles/blackwater-in-cambodia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 23:16:41 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://aan-news.proffer.dev/articles/blackwater-in-cambodia/</guid><description>Blackwater contractors on guard in Prei Khmaoch Luong. (AAN World News)
Some 200 contractors, working for Blackwater, have been operating throughout the province of Prei Khmaoch Luong since August, six months since their initial arrival in Cambodia.
Allegations have recently spread of a failed operation conducted by the private military company, which claimed the lives of 7 Cambodian soldiers. Although there is no current proof, the operation is suspected to be a show of force against the Royal Cambodian Navy after two IDAP employees were killed by Cambodian forces when delivering supplies to the local populace.</description></item></channel></rss>