<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Specialist Correspondent on AAN World News</title><link>https://3Mydlo3.github.io/aan-world-news/profiles/katherine-bishop/</link><description>Recent content in Specialist Correspondent on AAN World News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 11:06:45 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://3Mydlo3.github.io/aan-world-news/profiles/katherine-bishop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enquiry Fails to Find Cause of Livonian Training Disaster</title><link>https://3Mydlo3.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/livonian-training-disaster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 11:06:45 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://3Mydlo3.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/livonian-training-disaster/</guid><description>A US board of inquiry has said it is &amp;ldquo;very unlikely&amp;rdquo; Russian provocateurs were behind the June 19 training accident in Livonia. The incident occurred when a Greyhawk UAV overshot its target and dropped a GPS-guided bomb on a military site, claiming the lives of 1 American and 7 Livonia. Allegations of human error and a strongly-worded denial of responsibility from the white house have led to a collapse in US Livonian relations as well as a cancellation of the exercise themselves, creating a logistical nightmare and leaving 11,000 overseas personnel stranded.</description></item><item><title>Joint Russian-CSAT Exercise in Kaliningrad Heightens Tensions in Europe</title><link>https://3Mydlo3.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/joint-russian-csat-exercises/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 10:57:22 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://3Mydlo3.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/joint-russian-csat-exercises/</guid><description>CSAT troops take part in Russia joint military exercises led by the armed forces of Russia, CSAT’s defense ministry said on Wednesday. CSAT’s participation in the joint exercises was &amp;ldquo;unrelated to the current international and regional situation in the Mediterranean&amp;rdquo;, said Zhang Wei the Minister of CSAT. Last month, Moscow announced plans to hold a joint exercise with its new strategic partner CSAT from Aug. 7th to Sept. 30, even as the number of NATO troops in the Pacific Ocean continue to climb.</description></item><item><title>Skydive Over Tanoa</title><link>https://3Mydlo3.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/skydive-over-tanoa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 13:37:57 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://3Mydlo3.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/skydive-over-tanoa/</guid><description>AAN reporter Tom O&amp;rsquo;Connell in freefall over Tanoa. (AAN World News)
Skydiving is the new trend for tourists and locals alike in Tanoa. Sky Adventures, owned by Joni Madraiwiwi, recently restored three DC-3 aircraft for the business venture. With a staff of ten pilots and ten jump masters, Joni aims to have affordable jumps over Tanoa available throughout the summer season for qualified parachutists.
Sky Adventures&amp;rsquo;s jump masters offer weekly training courses every Monday and Wednesday.</description></item></channel></rss>