<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Asia on AAN World News</title><link>https://3Mydlo3.github.io/aan-world-news/tags/asia/</link><description>Recent content in Asia on AAN World News</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 09:17:32 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://3Mydlo3.github.io/aan-world-news/tags/asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NATO Forces Deploy to Dingor</title><link>https://3Mydlo3.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/nato-forces-deploy-to-dingor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 09:17:32 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://3Mydlo3.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/nato-forces-deploy-to-dingor/</guid><description>NATO soldiers on an airfield in Dingor. (AAN World News)
A combined NATO force of American, German, and Spanish troops have commenced operations following the first wave of deployments to the island nation of Dingor, according to US General and acting NATO commander William Coe.
Speaking at a press conference on Tuesday, General Coe briefed members of the media following the first week of operations undertaken by NATO forces on the island.</description></item><item><title>Blackwater in Cambodia</title><link>https://3Mydlo3.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/blackwater-in-cambodia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 23:16:41 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://3Mydlo3.github.io/aan-world-news/articles/blackwater-in-cambodia/</guid><description>Blackwater contractors on guard in Prei Khmaoch Luong. (AAN World News)
Some 200 contractors, working for Blackwater, have been operating throughout the province of Prei Khmaoch Luong since August, six months since their initial arrival in Cambodia.
Allegations have recently spread of a failed operation conducted by the private military company, which claimed the lives of 7 Cambodian soldiers. Although there is no current proof, the operation is suspected to be a show of force against the Royal Cambodian Navy after two IDAP employees were killed by Cambodian forces when delivering supplies to the local populace.</description></item></channel></rss>